Guide to the Language Resource Center collection, circa 1963-1983.
Language Resource Center collection,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Language Resource Center collection, circa 1963-1983.
14-18-4271
Cornell University Language Resource Center. Cornell University Language Resource Center
88 cubic feet.
Tape catalogs and tape recordings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Sound recordings and other materials used or produced by the Language Resource Center or otherwise related to their teaching of language at Cornell University.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
The Language Resource Center is a unit in Cornell University's College of Arts and Sciences that supports language teaching and learning.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Sound recordings and other materials used or produced by the Language Resource Center or otherwise related to their teaching of language at Cornell University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University Language Resource Center.
Subjects:
Language and languages.; Language Education.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Tape catalogs
Series II. Reel-to-reel tape recordings
CONTAINER LIST
- Tape catalogs, Undated
  - A-B, Undated (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - C, Undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - D, Undated (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - E, Undated (Box 89, Folder 4-6)
  - F, Undated (Box 89, Folder 7-8)
  - G, Undated (Box 89, Folder 9-10)
  - H, Undated (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - I, Undated (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - J, Undated (Box 89, Folder 13-14)
  - K, Undated (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - L, Undated (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - M, Undated (Box 89, Folder 17-19)
  - N-O, Undated (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - P-Q, Undated (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - R, Undated (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - S, Undated (Box 89, Folder 23-24)
  - T, Undated (Box 90, Folder 1-2)
  - U-V, Undated (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - W-Z, Undated (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Reel-to-reel tape recordings
  Guide has been arranged by series as designated by XXX when known.
  - Cornell material
    - German-Dialects, 1969; TR-11680; Kufuer, A.; 3.75, 1/2 back, master (Box 2)
      LRC #: GD 1
    - German-Dialects, 1969; TR-11681; Kufuer, A.; 3.75, 1/2 back, master (Box 2)
      LRC #: GD 2
    - German-Dialects, 1969; TR-11682; Kufuer, A.; 3.75, 1/2 back, master (Box 2)
      LRC #: GD 3
    - German-Dialects, 1969; TR-11683; Kufuer, A.; 3.75, 1/2 back, master (Box 2)
      LRC #: GD 4
    - German-Dialects, 1969; TR-11684; Kufuer, A.; 3.75, 1/2 back, master (Box 2)
      LRC #: GD 5
    - German-Dialects, 1969; TR-11685; Kufuer, A.; 3.75, 1/2 back, master (Box 2)
      LRC #: GD 6
    - Drei Kameraden, 1977-02-09; TR-11686; Cornell University; track a, 3.75, head tail foil, time use c-60. Recorded in DMLL booth. Duplicate (Box 2)
      LRC #: GQ 18.2
    - Drei Kameraden, 1977-02-09; TR-11687; Cornell University; track a, 3.75, head tail foil, time use c-90, recorded in DMLL booth. Duplicate (Box 2)
      LRC #: GQ 18.3
    - Drei Kameraden, 1977-02-09; TR-11688; Cornell Universiy; track a, 3.75, head tail foil, time use c-60. Recorded in DMLL booth. Duplicate (Box 2)
      LRC #: GQ 18.6
    - Mandarin Tape Quiz, 1983-03; TR-11689; Mangione, L.; exam, track a, 7.5 IPS, head tail foil, original (Box 3)
      Exam
      LRC #: MTQ 10
    - Mandarin Tape Quiz, 1977-12-05; TR-11690; Taylor, Wan-Fang; track a, head tail foil, dmll copyright, original, use c-45 (Box 3)
      Intermediate Chinese lessons 7-12 structure review quiz
      LRC #: MTQ 9
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, 1962-09-15; TR-11691; 3.75 IPS (Box 3)
      campus talks- introduction
      LRC #: MQ 1
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, 1974; TR-11692; Watson, Ronald; Shen, T.S.; 7.5 IPS (Box 3)
      1974 -75 Taipei language test (Mandarin Chinese) administered nationwide. Two part oral exam
      LRC #: MQ 2
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, 1974-03-05; TR-11693; Watson, Ronald; Shen, T.S.; 7.5 IPS, mono, half track, master (Box 3)
      Inter University Center Oral Exam
      LRC #: MQ 3
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, Undated; TR-11694; 7.5 IPS (Box 3)
      Mandarin Segmental Drills
      LRC #: MQ 4
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, Undated; TR-11695; 7.5 IPS (Box 3)
      Mandarin Tone Drills
      LRC #: MQ 5
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, Undated; TR-11696; Walton, R.; 7.5 IPS (Box 3)
      Edited. Mandarin 102 supplementary drill lesson 12. 2 comprehension stories
      LRC #: MQ 10
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, Undated; TR-11697; Walton, R.; 7.5 IPS (Box 3)
      Edited. Mandarin 102. supplementary drills lesson 14 and 15
      LRC #: MQ 11
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, Undated; TR-11698; Walton, R.; 7.5 IPS (Box 3)
      Edited. Mandarin supplementary drills 16 and 17
      LRC #: MQ 12
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, Undated; TR-11699; Walton, R.; 7.5 IPS (Box 3)
      Edited. Mandarin 102 supplementary drills lesson 18
      LRC #: MQ 13
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, 1973; TR-11700 (Box 3)
      Pronunciation tone drills, only last part=blank
      LRC #: MQ 6
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, Undated; TR-11701; 3.75 IPS (Box 3)
      Tape 16. Speak Chinese progressive exercises in Chinese pronunciation: track 1-lessons 10-17 track 2- lessons 7-9 and 18-21
      LRC #: MQ 7
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, Undated; TR-11702; Walton, R. (Box 3)
      Mandarin 101 supplementary drills lessons 10-11, to be edited
      LRC #: MQ 8
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, Undated; TR-11703; Walton, R.; 7.5 IPS (Box 3)
      Mandarin 102 supplementary drills lesson 13, edited, c-60
      LRC #: MQ 9
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, Undated; TR-11704; Walton, R.; 3.75 IPS (Box 3)
      Mandarin 101 pronunciation drill units 1and2, edited
      LRC #: MQ 14
    - Mandarin Supplemental Drills, Undated; TR-11705; Walton, R. (Box 3)
      Mandarin 101 pronunciation drills units 5, 6, 7, edited,
      LRC #: MQ 16
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11706; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 1
      LRC #: MR 1
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11707; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 10
      LRC #: MR 10
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11708; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 11
      LRC #: MR 11
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11709; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 12
      LRC #: MR 12
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11710; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 13
      LRC #: MR 13
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11711; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original lesson 14
      LRC #: MR 14
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11712; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 15
      LRC #: MR 15
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11713; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 2
      LRC #: MR 2
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11714; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 3
      LRC #: MR 3
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11715; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 4
      LRC #: MR 4
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11716; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 5
      LRC #: MR 5
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11717; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 6
      LRC #: MR 6
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11718; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 7
      LRC #: MR 7
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11719; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 8
      LRC #: MR 8
    - Read Chinese, 1981-09-18; TR-11720; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, lesson 9
      LRC #: MR 9
    - Read Chinese, 1981-10-14; TR-11721; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, Book III Lessons 1-2
      LRC #: MR 16
    - Read Chinese, 1981-10-14; TR-11722; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, Book III Lessons 3-5
      LRC #: MR 17
    - Read Chinese, 1981-10-14; TR-11723; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, Book III Lessons 10-12
      LRC #: MR 18
    - Read Chinese, 1981-10-14; TR-11724; Chang; 7.5 IPS, head tail foil (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang, track A, original, Book III Lessons 6-9
      LRC #: MR 19
    - Read Chinese, Undated; TR-11725; Chang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, foiled (Box 3)
      Read Chinese Book III lessons 13-18.
      LRC #: MR 20
    - Read Chinese, Undated; TR-11726; Chang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, foiled (Box 3)
      Read Chinese Book III lessons 19 and 20.
      LRC #: MR 21
    - Read Chinese, 1984-06-05; TR-11727; Chang; 7.5 speed, head tail foil, original (Box 3)
      Recorded by P. Wang. Book 2 dictation
      LRC #: MR 22
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11728; Huang; Lecture 1, 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled, 24 min (Box 4)
      LRC #: MT 1
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11729; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture 2
      LRC #: MT 2
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11730; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture3
      LRC #: MT 3
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11731; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture4
      LRC #: MT 4
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11732; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture5
      LRC #: MT 5
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11733; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture6
      LRC #: MT 6
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11734; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture8
      LRC #: MT 8
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11735; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      LRC #: MT 9
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11736; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture9
      LRC #: MT 10
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11737; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture10
      LRC #: MT 11
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11738; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture11
      LRC #: MT 13
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11739; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture12
      LRC #: MT 14
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11740; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      LRC #: MT 15
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11741; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture13
      LRC #: MT 16
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11742; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture14
      LRC #: MT 17
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11743; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture15
      LRC #: MT 18
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11744; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture16
      LRC #: MT 19
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11745; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture17
      LRC #: MT 20
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11746; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture18
      LRC #: MT 21
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11747; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture19
      LRC #: MT 23
    - Twenty Lectures in Chinese Culture, 1975-05-17; TR-11748; Huang; 3.75 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled (Box 4)
      lecture20
      LRC #: MT 24
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11749; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-90 (Box 4)
      lesson 10
      LRC #: HN 10
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11750; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      lesson 11 conv, thru A
      LRC #: HN 11.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11751; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-45 (Box 4)
      lesson 11 B-end
      LRC #: HN 11.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11752; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-45 (Box 4)
      lesson 12 conv, thru A
      LRC #: HN 12.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11753; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-45 (Box 4)
      lesson 12 B-end
      LRC #: HN 12.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11754; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-90 (Box 4)
      review lesson III A
      LRC #: HN 12.3
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11755; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-45 (Box 4)
      review lesson III B-end
      LRC #: HN 12.4
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11756; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-45 (Box 4)
      lesson 13 conv, thru A, revised 10/29/80
      LRC #: HN 13.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11757; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-45 (Box 4)
      lesson 13 B-end
      LRC #: HN 13.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11758; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      lesson 14 conv thru a
      LRC #: HN 14.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11759; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-45 (Box 4)
      track a, 7.5 IPS, original,c-45, lesson 14 B-end
      LRC #: HN 14.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11760; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      lesson 15 conv thru a
      LRC #: HN 15.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11761; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-45 (Box 4)
      lesson 15 B-end, revised 10/29/80
      LRC #: HN 15.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11762; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      lesson 16 conv thru a
      LRC #: HN 16.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11763; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      lesson 16 B-end
      LRC #: HN 16.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11764; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-45 (Box 4)
      review lesson 4, A.1-A.8
      LRC #: HN 16.3
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11765; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      review lesson 4, A.9-A.15
      LRC #: HN 16.4
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11766; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      reivew lesson 4, B-end
      LRC #: HN 16.5
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11767; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      lesson 17 conv thru A
      LRC #: HN 17.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11768; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-45 (Box 4)
      lesson 17, B-end
      LRC #: HN 17.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11769; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      lesson 18 conv thru A
      LRC #: HN 18.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11770; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      review lesson 5, B-end
      LRC #: HN 20.4
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11771; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      track a, 7.5 IPS, original, c-60,lesson 24 conv thru A.10
      LRC #: HN 24.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11772; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      lesson 24, A.11-end
      LRC #: HN 24.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11773; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      review lesson 6, A.1-A.12, new edit 10/27/80
      LRC #: HN 24.3
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-31; TR-11774; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      review lesson 6, A.13-end, new edit 10/27/80
      LRC #: HN 24.4
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11775; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      Review lesson I b-j, track a, original recording, revised 10/29/80
      LRC #: HN 4.3
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11776; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      lesson 5
      LRC #: HN 5
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11777; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      lesson 6
      LRC #: HN 6
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11778; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      lesson 7
      LRC #: HN 7
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11779; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-60 (Box 4)
      lesson 8. revised 10/29/80
      LRC #: HN 8.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11780; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-90 (Box 4)
      review lesson II
      LRC #: HN 8.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11781; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-45 (Box 4)
      lesson 9 conv through A
      LRC #: HN 9.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, 1980-07-25; TR-11782; Fairbanks; Misra; Cornell University Press; 7.5 IPS, original, c-45 (Box 4)
      lesson 9 - B to end
      LRC #: HN 9.2
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11783 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 10
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11784 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 11
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11785 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 12
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11786 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 13
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11787 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 14
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11788 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 15
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11789 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 16
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11790 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 17
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11791 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 8
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11792 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 9
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11793 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 38
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11794 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 39
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11795 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 40
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11796 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 41
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11797 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 18
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11798 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 19
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11799 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 20
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11800 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 21
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11801 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 22
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11802 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 23
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11803 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 24
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11804 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 25
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11805 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 26
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11806 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 27
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11807 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 28
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11808 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 29
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11809 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 3
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11810 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 30
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11811 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 31
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11812 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 32
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11813 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 33
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11814 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 34
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11815 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 35
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11816 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 36
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11817 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 37
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11818 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 1
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11819 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 2
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11820 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 4
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11821 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 5
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11822 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 6
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-11823 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TG 7
    - Spanish for the Hotel Industry, Undated; TR-11824 (Box 7)
      LRC #: SPD 1
    - Spanish for the Hotel Industry, Undated; TR-11825 (Box 7)
      LRC #: SPD 2
    - Spanish for the Hotel Industry, Undated; TR-11826 (Box 7)
      LRC #: SPD 3
    - Miscellaneous Spanish Material, Undated; TR-11827 (Box 7)
      LRC #: SPM 1
    - Spanish 123 Exercises, Undated; TR-11828 (Box 7)
      LRC #: SPE 1
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11829 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 1
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11830 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 2
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11831 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 3
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11832 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 10.1
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11833 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 10.2
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11834 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 11.1
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11835 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 4
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11836 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 5
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11837 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 6
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11838 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 7.1
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11839 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 7.2
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11840 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 8.1
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11841 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 8.2
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11842 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 9.1
    - Spanish Review Grammar, Undated; TR-11843 (Box 8)
      LRC #: SRG 9.2
    - Cuzco Quechua Master, Undated; TR-11844 (Box 10)
      LRC #: Q 1
    - Cuzco Quechua Dubbing Master, Undated; TR-11845 (Box 10)
    - Cuzco Quechua Master, Undated; TR-11846 (Box 10)
      LRC #: Q 10
    - Cuzco Quechua Dubbing Master, Undated; TR-11847 (Box 10)
    - Cuzco Quechua Master, Undated; TR-11848 (Box 10)
      LRC #: Q 11
    - Cuzco Quechua Dubbing Master, Undated; TR-11849 (Box 10)
    - Cuzco Quechua Master, Undated; TR-11850 (Box 10)
      LRC #: Q 12
    - Cuzco Quechua Dubbing Master, Undated; TR-11851 (Box 10)